

### Hello World.

I'm Seamus – a web developer with commercial experience in both front-end development and graphic design. I have been professionally building websites since 2018. I pride myself on being a fast learner and always seeking out new opportunities to improve my skills. My strong attention to detail and dedication to delivering quality work make me an asset to any project.



### Phone

+44 7702 174421



### **Fmail**

seamus@designbarn.co.uk

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2023 - Current

# Marketing Operations Specialist

HiveMinded, Manchester

2019 - Current

### **Web Developer**

Design Barn (freelance)

designbarn.co.uk

2018 - 2023

### **Digital Marketing Manager**

Open House (in-house), Bangor NI

courthousebangor.com openhousefestival.com openhousepresents.com At **HiveMinded** my role involves working with stakeholders to implement marketing plans through website updates and emails. My remit also includes developing new, better ways for the international team to work, for example to combat a repetitive typing task I created a chrome extension that simplifies, and speeds up the workflow.

**Design Barn** is my freelance business. I work with clients on every step from ordering a domain and setting up their hosting and emails to delivering a finished, responsive website with SEO, analytics and an easy to use CRM. Clients have ranged from a University led engineering project to charitable organisations and local businesses.

**Open House** is a live music venue, arts festival and non-profit. I worked on marketing campaigns, designed and maintained their websites and handled graphic design across festival launches, social media content and advertising materials. The project I'm most proud of was launching their new venue **The Court House**, for which I designed the brand styles, logo and website. The main challenge was building an events calendar system and I worked hard to make the site accessible, fast and have good SEO - with a focus on event schema.

## **SKILLS**

### **Web Development**

HTML, CSS, Js, React, Node, Git Next, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Wordpress

### **Graphic Design**

- Adobe CC - Ps, Ai, Ae, Xd, Id

### **Digital Marketing**

- Facebook/Instagram ads, SEO, copywriting

# **EDUCATION**

### **Front-end Web Development**

2022 - 2023 | EdX (Bootcamp) | 97%

### **Audio Engineering BSc**

2015 - 2018 | Queen's University of Belfast | 2:1

### **Music Technology**

2011 - 2013 | Leeds College of Music | A\* A\* A